vacationidea.com 2018-02-14

# VacationIdea.com Privacy Policy

This section explains our Privacy Policy so that you can have an understanding about the way information is collected and used by VacationIdea, LLC.

**The Information We Collect**  
VacationIdea, LLC provides a range of interactive user services, including but not limited to electronic greeting cards, e-mail this page to a friend, screensavers download, electronic newsletters, contests you can enter, voting in polls, online forums. Certain offerings, activities and parts of our network are only accessible and can only be used by persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include name and e-mail address. We do not collect personally identifying information about visitors except when knowingly provided by our visitors. 

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information, for example, the internet browser type, the type of operating system, the domain name of your Internet service provider, time spent on the web site, or referring link. 

**Use Of Information**  
The personal information that you provide is used to fulfill your requests, for example, email an electronic greeting card. The information is also used to respond to your inquiries and offer you other services that we feel may be of interest to you.

If you submit your comments or if you submit any other content, we may publish the information you have provided.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to government agencies or officials or other third parties if we believe such disclosure to be required under applicable law.

The non-personally identifiable information that we collect may be used to improve our services and to analyze the site usage and the usage of our content.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are text files place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. To enhance your experience, some of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering. Once you register, cookies may be used to personalize your experience at our web pages, for example, to recognize you by name when you return to our site and enable you to access the member only areas of our site.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites**  
This site contains links to other Internet sites that have their own privacy policies. VacationIdea, LLC has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by these third parties. 

**Advertising**  
VacationIdea, LLC may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see on our web site. The third-party ad servers we use may place cookies and/or collect non-personally identifiable information such as your internet browser type and the number of times you have viewed an ad. If you would like to opt-out, please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out page at http://aboutads.info/choices or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp .

**Notice to Parents**  
The site you are visiting is a general audience site.

**Miscellaneous**  
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

In the event that VacationIdea, LLC sells or transfers ownership, operation or control of its network, VacationIdea, LLC reserves the right to transfer or disclose all of its data to the buyer.

VacationIdea, LLC may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or concerns about theVacationIdea, LLC Privacy Policy you may contact us at sendcomment@vacationidea.com
